Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
- Porter, Carolyn A.
  - [Untitled], digital inset print; 1761; 324; "Asian Art Galleries, Museum of Fine Arts, Boston" 2001
- Postler, Klaus
  - [Untitled], 1762; 1121; Lawn sign
- Potter, Hayley
  - [Untitled], 1763; 1973; Statue of Liberty crying
- Potts, Igan, Kamlicar
  - [Untitled], text; 1763b; 3267
- Potts, Rebecca
  - [Untitled], 1764; 1180; Falling objects-glasses, lamp, etc.
- Power, Marc L.
  - [Untitled], 1765; 902; Ink blot
- Prachoinig, Maya
  - [Untitled], 1766; 923; Lines (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532)(Sent in 24 entries, but only these were used)
- Pregl, Arjan
  - [Untitled], 1767; 2032; Lots of colored dots
- Prescott, Tort
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1769; 1520; Close up of head of body cast (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532) (Sent in 24 entries, but only these were used)
- Prescott, Tort
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1770; 1521; Side view of photo of body cast (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532) (Sent in 24 entries, but only these were used)
- Prescott, Tort
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1771; 1522; Close up detail photo of body cast (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532) (Sent in 24 entries, but only these were used)
- Prescott, Tort
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1772; 1526; Close up detail photo of profile of body cast (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532) (Sent in 24 entries, but only these were used)
- Prescott, Tort
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1773; 1525; Photo of two body casts, one on top of the other (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532) (Sent in 24 entries, but only these were used)
- Prescott, Tort
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1774; 1531; Three images of sharks swimming (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532) (Sent in 24 entries total, but only these were used)
- Prescott, Tort
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1775; 1532; Photo of full size body cast (#'s 1520, 1521, 1522, 1525, 1526, 1531, 1532) (Sent in 24 entries total, but only these were used)
- Price, Rachel
  - [Untitled], 1776; 374; Student at Westchester Community College
- Prince, Lily
  - [Untitled], 1777; 1053; Small dots
- Pritzker, Elisa
  - Daily Routine Interrupted, computer graphic art; 1778; 1257; Computer generated images of male and female figures and airplanes over a map, bordered by text
- Prusko, David
  - [Untitled], 1779; 658
- Prusko, David
  - [Untitled], 1779b; 3326
- Prytyskacz, Jean
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1780; 2090; Photo of base of lampost
- Pugh Clark, Mary
  - [Untitled], collage; 1781; 1243
- Purvis, Polli
  - [Untitled], 1782; 914; Small photo with text on paper
- Pyke, Judith
  - [Untitled], 1783; 2145
- Quam, Lisa
  - [Untitled], comp print; 1785; 1980
- Raab, Michael
  - [Untitled], 1786; 349; "sometimes I imagine that this is all a part"
- Rabinovitch, Bill
  - Impact, computer generated image; 1787; 1067; Abstract image of a tower and an explosion of lines
- Rabner, Elliot
  - [Untitled], images on text; 1788; 834; Placed images onto the REACTIONS letter that EXIT ART sent out
- Rader, Terry
  - You Can Do Something, poem; 1790; 2251; Your living room...
- Radzetski, Pauel
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1791; 1640; Knife, blade pointed up and to the right
- Rahim, Quosia
  - [Untitled], 1792; 1529; Work on paper with 9 circles on top half with small etched marks inside and very small stick figures holding hands, forming chains, below.
- Rajer, Tony
  - [Untitled], 1793; 1142; "around 3am..."
- Ramer, Jim
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1794; 1485; Photo of cloudy sky with the silouettes of three people at the bottom
- Ramjauer, Birgit
  - [Untitled], 1795; 22; Dropped off in person--part of 3 sister's installation--tape collage/poetry
- Ramjauer, Ilse
  - [Untitled], 1796; 24; Dropped off in person - part of 3 sister's installation--tape collage/poetry
- Ramjauer, Maria
  - [Untitled], 1797; 23; Dropped off in person--part of 3 sister's installation--tape collage/poetry needs to change size
- Ranard, John
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1798; 1780; Blurred flag
- Ranard, John
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1799; 1781; Photo of daily news
- Ranard, John
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1800; 1782; Flag
- Ranard, John
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1801; 1783; Flag on car
- Rand, Alan
  - [Untitled], photo and poem on gold painted paper; 1802; 1348; Each generation suffers
- Ranard, John
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1802b; 1784; Wrapped building
- Randolph, Sal
  - [Untitled], 1803; 475
- Rantzer, Philip
  - [Untitled], artwork; 1804; 67; Via mail
- Rapp, Ray
  - Raw, 1805; 198; (chicken)
- Rappel
  - [Untitled], 1806; 239; "I find myself thinking more about history..."
- Rassouli, Manazar
  - [Untitled], 1807; 1222; There are many ways...
- Ratner, Rochelle
  - Bride, photograph; 1809; 755; An image of a manequin wearing a bride's dress in a store window
- Raven, Tamara
  - Humanity, 1810; 592
- Ravenna, Cristiana Moldi
  - [Untitled], 1811; 184; Prose "we should beter follow the crickets..."
- Raza, Abbas
  - Gotham 9/11/01, 1812; 132
- Razdow, Max
  - Fear City, Sky Army, copy of painting, acrylic on two board panels; 1813; 512
- Rebecca & Sandra
  - [Untitled], 1814; 544; 15 of 16
- Recht, Marylin
  - [Untitled], 1815; 361; Diary excerpt "east village, 9/13/01..."
- Rechtschaffer, Sheilah
  - Memory Never Forgotten, ink and collaged Chinese paper; 1816; 1506
- Reed, Jesse F.
  - Back to Normal: Day #7, photograph; 1817; 2104; Photo of woman holding mail w/gloves on (1 of 2)
- Reed, Jesse F.
  - Back to Normal: Day #1, photograph; 1818; 2105; Photo of woman opening mailbox w/gloves on (1 of 2)
- Rees, Sue
  - [Untitled], 1819; 616; "woke up at 6:30..."
- Regan, Betsey
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1820; 1428; Abstract painting; a hanging bull in upper right hand corner
- Regan, Paul
  - King with Sun and Moon Trees and B-2 Bomber, micro piezo print; 1821; 26; Sent via mail
- Regas, Melissa
  - [Untitled], 1822; 379; Grad at Cal Arts
- Reichardt, Kelly
  - [Untitled], 1823; 227; 1 of 4 notebook pages with magazine cutouts
- Reichardt, Kelly
  - [Untitled], 1824; 228; 2 of 4 notebook pages with magazine cutouts
- Reichardt, Kelly
  - [Untitled], 1825; 229; 3 of 4 notebook pages with magazine cutouts
- Reichardt, Kelly
  - [Untitled], 1826; 230; 4 of 4 notebook pages with magazine cutouts
- Reilly, Natasha
  - [Untitled], 1827; 3022; Image of friend on left, text on right
- Reinstead, Dea
  - Memoranda, 1828; 523; Flag and face 1 of 2
- Reinsteid, Dea
  - In My Dream, text on paper; 1829; 522; 10 line poem
- Reis, Lori
  - Waiting to be Found, digital image; 1830; 870
- Reiser, Daniel
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1831; 1100; Photograph of a Marine posing with a young boy on a city street
- Rem, Greg
  - [Untitled], 1832; 886; Man with hands behind his back
- Renfrow, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1833; 713; "Dollars for terror herion chic"
- Renko, Lisa
  - Carvel, painting; 1834; 1629; Carvel Ice Cream logo
- Ressler, Oliver
  - [Untitled], 1835; 170; Project Boom! "www.ifonly people..."
- Restany & Panseca, Pierre & Filippo
  - Merry Christmas America, 1836; 1005; Image of Twin Towers of Light with text at top
- Reynolds
  - [Untitled], 1837; 519; Flowers drawing
- Reynolds, David
  - The Wishing Well, mixed media; 1838; 1370; Abstract drawing with "The Wishing Well" in center
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - The Count of God's Angels Increase, 1839; 1727; 1727-1738; "as the fateful day arrived..."
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Firemen Heroes, 1840; 1728; 1727-1738
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Angel, 1841; 1729; 1727-1738
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Hope for Ground Zero, 1842; 1730; 1727-1738
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - The Fight, 1843; 1731; 1727-1738; apple candle
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Angels Watching, 1844; 1732; 1727-1738
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Peace on Earth, 1845; 1733; 1727-1738
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - In Memorial, 1846; 1734; 1727-1738; twin tower candles
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Hope, 1847; 1735; 1727-1738
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Protecting Angel, 1848; 1736; 1727-1738
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Day to Remember, 1849; 1737; 1727-1738;"six thousand stars..."
- Rhoads, Eirene
  - Angels Over the City, 1850; 1738; 1727-1738
- Ribuffo, Susana
  - 11, 1852; 1237
- Ricchiardi, John
  - [Untitled], newspaper collage; 1852b; 1287
- Riccardi, Andrea
  - [Untitled], color copy; 1852b; 3255
- Riccardi, Andrea
  - [Untitled], color copy; 1852c; 3258
- Richard, Paul
  - It Takes a Child to Raze a Village, 1853; 3099
- Ridgeway, James
  - The Crayons are Nontoxic, text on paper; 1854; 1093; Poem on paper
- Ridgway, Renee
  - Buck Teeth, 1855; 2015; Dead beaver
- Riedman, Emily
  - [Untitled], 1856; 372
- Rifas, Karen
  - nine/eleven, stiched oak leaves; 1857; 1694
- Riley, Elizabeth
  - [Untitled], ink, snapshots and digital image; 1858; 788
- Ring, Lazlo
  - Sept. 11, 2001, 1859; 2020; WTC w/gun
- Ring, Ray
  - [Untitled], 1860; 2033; Triangles of paper
- Ritchfield, C.
  - Where's the joy? Joyce?, mixed media; 1861; 1254; Text: "I'm okay. O.k.fine, you? O.K. Fine, you?"
- Rivera, Ryan
  - [Untitled], xerox; 1862; 508; W/gas mask
- Rizer, Leah
  - [Untitled], 1863; 557; 3 of 16
- Roberts, Marie A.
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 1864; 2108; Abstract drawing of Ground Zero
- Robinson, Clay
  - [Untitled], 1866; 586; Arrows
- Robinson, Frank
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1867; 832; One written line in script
- Robinson, Joshua
  - [Untitled], 1868; 194
- Rocha, Patrick
  - September Eleventh 2001, pen on paper; 1869; 1377; Drawings of sullen men and woman with the twin towers on a cloud in the sky
- Roderick, Irene
  - [Untitled], oil on canvas; 1870; 325; Untitled 2001 collage
- Rodriguez, Cynthia
  - Common Bond, 1872; 1974; Osama or bust
- Roerdink, Ria
  - I Can't Find You Shadow, 1873; 1195
- Rojas, Alexandra
  - Guilty, pencil on paper; 1874; 1081; The word "GUILTY" written by hand on paper
- Rolnick, Diane G.
  - [Untitled], text and paint; 1875; 507
- Roloff, Stefan
  - Trophy, 1876; 285; Images of mounted deer
- Roman, William
  - [Untitled], 1877; 558; 2 of 16
- Romans, Beth
  - [Untitled], artwork, text; 1878; 120; Via email
- Romero, Carlos
  - [Untitled], 1879; 1442; Dove and American flag
- Romero, Carlos
  - [Untitled], 1880; 1446; Head in star
- Romero, J.C.
  - [Untitled], 1881; 1650; Comparison of missing persons 30000/5000 "The Search: Grandmother's Mother's Son's" "Analogy Terrorismo
- Roniger, Taney
  - [Untitled], paper; 1882; 1406; Braille like arrangement of dots on white paper
- Ronse, Tom
  - And the Wind Began to Howl..., 1883; 524
- Ronzon, Estrella Carmona
  - Ballistic Statue (Tribute to New York City), gouasche on paper; 1884; 765
- Roos, Katrin
  - Match in heaven, photos of art piece; 1884b; 1645; 3 photos of painted match books
- Ros, Moses
  - Deep Impact, tempura on photocopy; 1885; 684
- Rosario, Cassandra
  - [Untitled], 1886; 553; 7 of 16
- Rosas, Melcina
  - Horror in New York City, digital image; 1888; 799; Images and text www.melcinarosas.com
- Rose, Cherith
  - [Untitled], drawing; 1889; 355
- Rose, Coralee Lynn
  - [Untitled], 1890; 1568
- Rose, Ruth
  - This Year I Will:, mixed media; 1891; 1412; Collage of WTC disaster photos and cut out printed text
- Rosenbaum, Daniel
  - [Untitled], verhead map image; 1893; 1372
- Rosenberg, Halsman
  - [Untitled], 1894; 492
- Rosenberg, Terry
  - [Untitled], 1895; 3008
- Roser, Lorin
  - [Untitled], computer ink jet and pencil; 1896; 855; WTC photo
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1897; 2061; Three figures standing (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1898; 2060; Drawing of Guiliani standing in crowd. (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1899; 2062; Drawing of Ground Zero; two small figures in foreground (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1900; 2063; Drawing of Chicago policewoman talking to Muslim woman (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1901; 2064; Train abstraction (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1902; 2065; Two planes in sky (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1903; 2066; Drawing of firemen carrying a body on a stretcher (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1904; 2067; Drawing of 2 men talking (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1905; 2068; Drawing of Afghan soldiers (#'s 2060-2069)
- Roske, Rachel
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1906; 2069; Drawing of two Arab men on left (#'s 2060-2069)
- Ross, Robert
  - We Are One, poem; 1908; 2133; Peace love Hope grace...
- Rosser, Phyllis F.
  - Reactions, text on paper; 1909; 795; Short essay
- Rossi, John
  - [Untitled], printed text on paper; 1910; 760; 6 boxes of text
- Rossler, Sillia
  - Today and Forever, photo and text; 1911; 1140
- Roth Sullivan, Heather
  - [Untitled], 1912; 1150; Man with ties
- Rourke, James
  - [Untitled], 1913; 1226
- Roussel, Eugenie
  - One, fabric, thread, and beads; 1914; 1079; A white fabric piece with the word "one" embroidered in the center
- Rowe Harrison, Susan
  - [Untitled], 1915; 2122
- Kaz, Roxanne
  - One September Morning, poem; 1916; 2180; September morning quickly changed...
- Royval, Rudy
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1917; 1556; Fingers w/smiley face
- Royval, Mr.
  - [Untitled], drawing; 1917a; 3290; Campestr elementary
- Rozynski, Wojceich
  - [Untitled], 1917b; 3200
- Rubio, Marta
  - Tragedy Strikes Madrid, 1919; 3015; Poem via email
- Ruff, Donna
  - [Untitled], 1920; 572; Torn phone book
- Rule, Charlene
  - Bag Lady, printed text on paper; 1921; 1068; A short essay on white paper
- Rupp, Christy
  - Viruses are saved from extinction - Creation Myth for the next era, photograph and text; 1922; 991; Photograph of toy helicopter with toy creatures around it; 7 lines of text underneath the photo ChristyRupp.com
- Rush, Arlene
  - [Untitled], 1923; 488; Many heads 1 of 2
- Rush, Arlene
  - Peace, 1924; 487; One head 2 of 2
- Ruth, Tara
  - Ohno, 1925; 2033; Ball on road
- Rutter, Ana
  - [Untitled], thread on paper; 1926; 822; Thread sewn in a vertical line down center of paper
- Rutter, Ana
  - [Untitled], 1927; 1339; Clothing
- Rutzky, Jeffrey
  - [Untitled], 1928; 640; Reflection of WTC in another building
- Ryan, Shawna
  - Rilke was Right, poem; 1929; 3083
- Ryan, Terri
  - [Untitled], text; 1930; 15; Via email
- Ryu, Okee
  - Unpolitical Waenning, mixed media on paper bag; 1931; 2047; 4 lb bag next to a crossed out banana
- Saccomandi, Monica
  - Anetesia, photographs; 1932; 1001; 7 photographs arranged vertically down center of page of a woman walking down a busy street with her eyes closed
- Sage, Alexander
  - Peace in Accord, 1933; 214
- Sakurai, Kenn
  - [Untitled], 1934; 433; There is a beauty here
- Saleme, Nancy
  - [Untitled], 1935; 1510; Face
- Salmanson, Carol
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1936; 761; Line drawing
- Samarthya, Ambika
  - Always in Our Hearts, 1937; 1720; Twin towers drawn in black, East Harlem Hip Hop activism class. (1720-1726)
- Rogers, Ronnie
  - Everyone was cool, everyone was chillin'..., poem; 1938; 1721; "Everyone was cool...", from Ambika Samarthya's East Harlem Hip Hop activism class. (1720-1726)
- Fluellen, Shequila
  - [Untitled], text; 1939; 1722; "My heart goes out...", from Ambika Samarthya's East Harlem Hip Hop activism class. (1720-1726)
- Ferguson, Keora
  - [Untitled], 1940; 1723; "I don't care...", from Ambika Samarthya's East Harlem Hip Hop activism class. (1720-1726)
- Crawford, Zaqia
  - Turn 2 Music, marker on paper; 1941; 1724; "Hope Peace Turn 2 Music...", from Ambika Samarthya's East Harlem Hip Hop activism class. (1720-1726)
- Obando, Desiree
  - Learning, marker on paper; 1942; 1725; "As I sit and listen...", from Ambika Samarthya's East Harlem Hip Hop activism class. (1720-1726)
- Yancy, Whitney
  - World Peace, marker on paper; 1943; 1726; "All of the hatred...", from Ambika Samarthya's East Harlem Hip Hop activism class. (1720-1726)
- Samelson, Andra
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1944; 1425; Abstract image of human figure in center w/dark background
- Studio Project, Open
  - [Untitled], collage on orange paper; 1945; 1315
- Sampson Bieberich, Ginny
  - [Untitled], 1946; 1861; Angular face
- Sanabria, Oscar M.
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1947; 983; Photo of man from shoulders up looking towards the right with a small plane flying into his ear
- Sandberg, Blake
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 1948; 2110; Abstract design w/skull in lower left hand corner
- Sandberg, Blake
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 1949; 2109; Drawing of traffic light with word "collapse" on bottom
- Sanders, Sophie
  - Movements of the Heart, 1950; 1184; More than we can bear
- Sandolin, D.
  - [Untitled], 1951; 1191; Pit of sorrow
- Santa Cecilia, Maria
  - [Untitled], pencil and ink on paper; 1952; 1450; Abstract pencil drawing of fragmented shapes
- Santiago, Michael
  - [Untitled], 1953; 545; 14 of 16
- Santos Rocha, Eliane
  - [Untitled], etching (aquatint); 1954; 1920
- Sapien, Darryl
  - Serenade, 1956; 2039; Figure playing violin over city
- Sarafin, Peter
  - [Untitled], 1957; 643; "Why does God..."
- Saraka, Anna
  - [Untitled], 1958; 3026; Text in Italian
- Sargent, Emily
  - [Untitled], 1959; 1740; I "heart" NY
- Sarkar Ellias, Bina
  - 9/11, The Year of Babel, poem; 1960; 2136; Dust has not sttled.
- Sasaki, Jonathan
  - [Untitled], photo collage; 1961; 685
- Sassi, Maria
  - Sonnet on the Season of War and Ice, 1962; 1244; "This is the last..."
- Sastre, Martin
  - Gonne with the Wind, 1963; 2002
- Saunders, Howard
  - [Untitled], 1964; 847; Who you gonna call
- Saunders, Howard
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1965; 960; "hey, bucky"
- Savage, Tom
  - Resurrection: Two Weeks After WTC & A Small Poem Against Fear, text on paper; 1966; 1453; Two poems on same page
- Gae, Savannah
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1966b; 3323; Feathers
- Sayler, William B.
  - [Untitled], 1967; 1131; 16 small images arranged horizontally w/text at top and bottom
- Sbano, Diane
  - Rescue Dog, laser print, colored paper, glitter; 1968; 885; Photo of a hand crafted dog with paper, glitter, and metallic stars
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1969; 483; Small circle of W Bush as superhero 1 of 8
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1970; 482; Gas mask 2 of 8
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1971; 481; Butt shot 3 of 8
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1972; 480; "Hello my name..." 4 of 8
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1973; 479; "Dumbell..." 5 of 8
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1974; 478; Puffy arms and legs 6 of 8
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1975; 477
- Scala, Robert
  - [Untitled], 1976; 476; Two profiles 7 of 8
- Scannell, Aine
  - Frozen Psyche, 1979; 378
- Scarrilt, Alan
  - [Untitled], 1980; 744; Image of twin towers
- Schaer, Miriam
  - Float, acrylic on paper; 1981; 3096; Gold dress in middle of page
- Schafer, Anja
  - [Untitled], 1983; 189; "You are a thousand moments of shadow and light..."
- Schaller, Rhonda
  - I'm okay, 1985; 596; Dark
- Schaller, Rhonda
  - I'm ok, 1986; 595; Pfdsd, abscoexist
- Schechter, Naomi
  - Carrie Progen: The Subway Sketch Artist and Her Fellow Travelers, 1987; 1148; Small pic. of Carrie
- Schechter, Naomi
  - Carrie Progen: The Subway Sketch Artist and Her Fellow Travelers, 1988; 1147; Larger photo of Carrie
- Scheier, Graciela
  - [Untitled], 1989; 2290; Do people in the USA...
- Schifano, Karen
  - [Untitled], 1990; 742
- Schiff, Clay
  - [Untitled], 1991; 1511
- Schiff, Jeffrey
  - [Untitled], 1992; 2046; Abstract design
- Schiff, Walker
  - [Untitled], 1993; 1508; Sitting man and black blocks
- Schleisner, Mark
  - [Untitled], 1994; 1173; "after the second tower..."
- Schneemann, Carolee
  - Seven Scans - WTC, 1995; 1739; Images of people falling from towers. "Permission to see. This visual concentration as eulogy, a mediation..."
- Schneider, Rosalind
  - Aftermath, 1996; 1160; "stranger talk..."
- Schonhoff, Michael
  - Carts, Caps, and Punches, mixed media collage; 1997; 2205
- Schreiber-Noll, Ilse
  - September 11, 2001, photomontage; 1998; 393
- Schwalb, Susan
  - A Report from New York, 1999; 3048; "Although I have lived for a number..."
- Schwalb, Susan
  - [Untitled], color copy; 1999b; 3207
- Schwolsky, Elena
  - Before and After, text; 2000; 1579; "for the past week in NYC..."
- Schworm, Julie B.
  - [Untitled], 2001; 747
- Scott, April
  - [Untitled], collage of texts; 2002; 649
- Scott, Dread
  - [Untitled], 2003; 1132; "Feel explosions..." 1 of 2
- Scott, Dread
  - [Untitled], 2004; 1133; List of names cut off at edge of paper 2 of 2
- Scott, Whitney
  - Recipe for Christmas Cake, 2001, 2006; 2163
- Seeman, Bonnie
  - [Untitled], 2007; 723
- Seid, Dui
  - How to Foil a Hijacking, 2008; 620
- Seidel, Douglas
  - Of The Six Thousand, text on paper; 2009; 830; 7 stanza poem
- Selby, Todd
  - [Untitled], color print; 2009b; 3224
- Seligson, Judith
  - [Untitled], iris print of original painting; 2010; 858
- Semmons, Carol
  - Failures of the heart, collage; 2010b; 3236
- Seng, Bob
  - EXIT 360, 2011; 1357
- Seo, Jinnie
  - Kind of Blue, 2012; 1187; Full page of horizontal bands
- Servon, Jody
  - [Untitled], text and digital image; 2013; 1061; Text is a dialogue between two people, imposed over a map of the U.S.
- Shafi, Asma
  - [Untitled], 2014; 267
- Shahrokh, Naz
  - Reaction/Experience from 9/11-Thinking of Ginsberg, sunflower heart pollen, miracle grow, gesso, graphite on paper; 2015; 1050
- Shalom
  - [Untitled], 2016; 1718; Image of tower exploding with first line of poetry "The night after the giant beacon imploded..."
- Shapiro, Amy
  - [Untitled], digital image with text; 2017; 1603; Short essay over an image of a female face
- Shapiro, Natasha
  - [Untitled], oil pastel, ink and scotch tape; 2018; 1634; Three dark squares, stacked vertically
- Sharom, Miriam
  - Remember me!, collage; 2018b; 3249; Mylar w/"remember me" covering a collage picture of people
- Shaw, Gary
  - [Untitled], 2019; 254; Pink dots
- Shefhan, James
  - [Untitled], 2020; 1540; Bottom half of photocopied date book with photograph of Bin Laden and councelors with image of towers drawn over it
- Shefhan, James
  - [Untitled], photocopy; 2021; 1541; Date book with photographs of banner that reads, "Americans, Think! Why You Are Hated All Over the World"
- Shefhan, James
  - [Untitled], photocopy; 2022; 1542; Date book September 10-12, the entry area for the 11th has been scratched out
- Shelle, Suzy
  - Collapsing Buildings, 2023; 918
- Shergill, Satyajit
  - A Shame to Humanity, 2024; 599; Squiggle people and buildings
- Sherman, Gary
  - [Untitled], 2025; 3082; Record/record
- Sherrod, Thomas
  - [Untitled], 2026; 439; Teddy bear and deer
- Shido, Kayo
  - [Untitled], 2027; 1856; Lots of people
- Shim, David
  - [Untitled], 2028; 3033
- Shimizu, Yuko
  - [Untitled], 2029; 1251; Fire truck
- Shin, Hyungsub
  - [Untitled], photo collage; 2030; 888; Various photos of the WTC collaged together
- Shin, Jean
  - Collapsed 9-11-2001, 2031; 278
- Shin, Kyungmi
  - Superman, 2032; 2014; 4 images, one superman
- Shiraka, Yoshio
  - [Untitled], 2033; 2219; Man and globe
- Shire, Ellen
  - [Untitled], 2034; 693; Triangle in middle of page
- Shirobayashi, Kiriko
  - [Untitled], 2035; 712; Dead bunnies
- Shoemaker, Pam
  - [Untitled], 2036; 100; Text letter and drawing www.pamshoemaker.net
- Shore, Paul
  - [Untitled], 2037; 124; Artwork via mail
- Sibert, Philippa
  - [Untitled], 2038; 856
- Sider, Sandra
  - [Untitled], 2039; 98; Artwork via mail www.photoquilt.net
- Sigler, Sequoia Megary
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 2040; 769; Text: WAR is not the answer to our pain; it just obscures the questions
- Sigurdardottir, Katrin
  - [Untitled], 2041; 1233; Photos of NYC skyline
- Sigurdsson, Sigurdur Thoris
  - [Untitled], 2042; 498; Cone head drawing 1 of 2
- Sigurdsson, Sigurdur Thoris
  - [Untitled], 2043; 497; Drawing 2 of 2
- Silver, M.